AD.MC.028
AbuDhabi
- A priest walking in the desert in Helwan. 12.7 x 17.7 cm, Circa 1900; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref135)
  Arabic Writing; Column/Colonnade; Deserts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing
- A man posing in an ornate uniform and tarbouche with a sword. 17.8 x 11.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref136)
  Fezes/Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Gloves; Helwan, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Swords & Knives; Uniforms
- Boys standing in front of a former casino building. 12.9 x 12.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref137)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Boys; Buildings; Casino; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints
- Group portrait of students and teachers. 11.4 x 17.6 cm, Circa 1910; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref138)
  Arabic Writing; Buildings; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Class portrait with Father Cremono, Father Minoli and Father Ghirotto. 17.8 x 24 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref139)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Ties; Women
- Class portrait with students and teachers. 16.8 x 23.5 cm, 1956-1957; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref140)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education; Shorts; Students; Teachers; Women
- Class portrait. 14 x 19.3 cm, 1961-1962; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref141)
  Boys; Children; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Moustaches; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Ties
- Class portrait. 17.8 x 24.5 cm, 1957-1958; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref142)
  Arabic Writing; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women
- Porch of Princess Khadeeja's (Emina Ilhamy) villa. 24.3 x 18 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref143)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Ornaments; Photographic Prints
- Facade of the College de la Sainte Famille. 17.9 x 23.3 cm, 1888; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref144)
  Architecture; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Students; Windows
- Dormitory of the College de la Sainte Famille. 17.9 x 23.9 cm, Circa 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref145)
- Theater of the College de la Sainte Famille. 18 x 24 cm, 1937; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref146)
  Arabic Writing; Chairs; Flags; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Insignia/Emblem; Interiors; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Pianos; Religious Crosses; Schools/Education; Stage; Theater
- Dormitory of the College de la Sainte Famille. 22.8 x 17.9 cm, 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref147)
- The College de la Sainte Famille building. 18 x 24 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref148)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Doors; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education
- Father Minoli, the school director, working in his office. 17.8 x 23.8 cm, 1940-1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref149)
  Arabic Writing; Chairs; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Italian Writing; Offices; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Religious Crosses; Schools/Education
- Class portrait. 17.8 x 24 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref150)
  Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Insignia/Emblem; Italian Writing; Men; Moustaches; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Group portrait of the school band with teachers. 11.5 x 17.2 cm, Circa 1910; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref151)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Brass Instruments; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Music; Musical Instruments; Musicians; Orchestra; Performing arts; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Woodwind Instruments
- Group portrait of men in military uniforms. 11.7 x 17.7 cm, Circa 1900; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref152)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Fezes/Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Insignia/Emblem; Italian Writing; Men; Military/Soldiers; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Uniforms
- The church of Sainte Famille in Helwan. 11.7 x 17.9 cm, Circa 1900; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref153)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Churches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites
- Group portrait of the school orchestra. 12.3 x 15.3 cm, Circa 1910; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref154)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Brass Instruments; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Music; Musical Instruments; Orchestra; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Religious Crosses; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Woodwind Instruments
- Group portrait of the school orchestra. 11.3 x 18 cm, Circa 1910; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref155)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Brass Instruments; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Music; Musical Instruments; Orchestra; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Group portrait of students wearing theatrical costumes. 11.7 x 18 cm, Circa 1910; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref156)
  Actors; Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Costumes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Painted Backdrops; Performance Plays; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Theater; Wigs
- Street view of the Tewfiq Mosque secondary school in Helwan. 24.3 x 18 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref157)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Islamic Architecture; Italian Writing; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Schools/Education; Streets/Roads
- Portrait of Mr. Laurella. 19.3 x 13.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref158)
  Albumen Prints; Arabic Writing; Bow Ties; Carte de Visite/Cabinet Card; Helwan, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Italian Writing; Men; Moustaches; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- Class portrait. 13.9 x 19.2 cm, 1960-1961; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref159)
  Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Moustaches; Priests; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Ties
- Group portrait of the sports team. 18.1 x 23.9 cm, 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref160)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Football; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Sports; Sports Kit/Sportswear; Sports teams; Students
- Group portrait of the workers of the school theater with Father Lafrauchi and Father Boromi. 17.2 x 23. 3cm, 1937; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref161)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Costumes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Performing arts; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education; Teachers; Theater; Workers
- Group portrait of students with Father Lighuoretti on a beach in Suez. 17.9 x 23.9 cm, Circa 1948; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref162)
  Arabic Writing; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Beaches; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Red Sea; Schools/Education; Seas; Students; Suez, Egypt; Teachers; Umbrellas/Parasols
- Students playing football on a field. 15.6 x 24 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref163)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Fields; Football; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Sports; Sports Kit/Sportswear; Sports teams; Students
- Group portrait of teachers taken during an excursion to the Petrified Forest. 17.9 x 23.9 cm, Circa 1932; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref164)
  Arabic Writing; Cameras; Deserts; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Landscapes; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Religious Crosses; Schools/Education; Teachers
- Group portrait of students and teachers during a field trip to the Japanese Gardens. 17.9 x 23.9 cm, Circa 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref165)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Pond; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Water
- Class portrait. 17.1 x 23. 5 cm, 1957-1958; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref166)
  Arabic Writing; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- View of the Church of the Holy Family. 22.9 x 16.4 cm, Circa 1920; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref167)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Churches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Religious Crosses; Religious Sites; Streets/Roads
- Building of the school theater in Helwan. 17.3 x 24 cm, 1937; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref168)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Column/Colonnade; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Theater
- Elevated street view of a school from Roston Street No. 28. 18 x 24.1 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref169)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Streets/Roads
- Street view of 'Casa Bugeya' in the Suez Canal previously known as the 'Chelsea Pension'. 16.3 x 23.7 cm, April 26th 1946; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref170)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Balcony/Terrace; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Hotels; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Suez, Egypt
- The Helwan Observatory building. 16.6 x 23.9 cm, 1903; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref171)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Observatory; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Telescope
- Class portrait. 17.9 x 23.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref172)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Group portrait of students climbing a rock during a field trip. 9.4 x 14.4 cm, 1951; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref173)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Field-trip; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Group portrait of students with teachers during a visit to Suez. 9.3 x 14.5 cm, 1955; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref174)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Field-trip; Fountains; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education; Students; Suez, Egypt; Teachers
- Street view of 'Evergreen' hotel. 8.6 x 13.6 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref175)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Cars; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Hotels; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Windows
- Group portrait of men in the gardens of the sulphureous bath house in Helwan. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1888; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref176)
  Arabic Writing; Baths; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Nature; Photographic Prints; Springs
- Class portrait. 14.5 x 19.4 cm, 1961-1962; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref177)
  Arabic Writing; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Street view of Tawfiq Mosque in Helwan finished in 1884. 17.7 x 12.6 cm, Circa 1900; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref178)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Islamic Architecture; Italian Writing; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites
- The school refrectory with a fully prepared dining table. 17.8 x 23.6 cm, Circa 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref179)
  Arabic Writing; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Interiors; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Photographs; Schools/Education; Tables
- Two students at the beach during a field trip to Suez. 17.8 x 23.8 cm, 1946; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref180)
  Arabic Writing; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Beaches; Boys; Children; Field-trip; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Red Sea; Students; Suez, Egypt
- Students in during a field trip to Ain Helwan (Capritage) springs with Father Puppi. 24 x 18 cm, Circa 1950-1951; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref181)
  Arabic Writing; Baths; Boys; Children; Field-trip; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Springs; Students
- First 'Capritage' swimming pond in Helwan. 15.5 x 24 cm, Circa 1947; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref182)
  Arabic Writing; Baths; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Pond; Springs; Swimming Pools
- Street view of 'Des Princes' hotel at 16 Ibrahim Street. 16.5 x 24 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref183)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Hotels; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads
- Group portrait of students on the bridge in the Japanese Gardens in Helwan. 17.8 x 23.9 cm, Circa 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref184)
  Arabic Writing; Bridges; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Nature; Photographic Prints; Pond; Schools/Education; Students; Water
- Entrance to the College de la Sainte Famille with Father Francerehi standing at the gates. 18 x 24 cm, Circa 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref185)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education; Streets/Roads
- The funeral procession of Father Carimuro Giacomelli on Mansur Street, Helwan. 16.6 x 23.9 cm, November 1924; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref186)
  Animals; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Carriages/Coaches; Coffins/Caskets; Funeral Proceedings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Horses; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads
- Class portrait of students with two teachers. 17.9 x 23.8 cm, 1958-1959; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref187)
- Students playing football in the school playground. 17.8 x 23.9 cm, Circa 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref188)
  Arabic Writing; Children; Football; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Sports; Students
- Students dancing in the school playground. 16.7 x 23.9 cm, Circa 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref189)
  Arabic Writing; Children; Dancing; Football; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Nuns; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students
- Student Mario Abdel Galil receiving a medal from Father Vantini during the graduation ceremony. 17.7 x 24 cm, Circa 1953; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref190)
  Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Graduation Ceremony; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Nuns; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Religious Crosses; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Women
- Father posing with students and workers in a group portrait during a field trip. 17.8 x 23.8 cm, 1936-1937; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref191)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Fezes/Tarbouches; Field-trip; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Religious Crosses; Schools/Education; Students; Workers
- Group portrait of students on a camel during a field trip to Giza. 18 x 23.9 cm, Circa 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref192)
  Animals; Arabic Writing; Boys; Camels; Field-trip; Gelatin Silver Prints; Giza, Egypt; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Pyramids; Pyramids of Giza; Students
- Entrance to Tawfiq Mosque in Helwan. 24 x 17.9 cm, 1884; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref193)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Entrance; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Islamic Architecture; Italian Writing; Mosques; Photographic Prints
- Sulphur Spring in Helwan. 24 x 18.1 cm, 1884; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref194)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Baths; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Springs
- Group portrait of students on 26 Sharif Street in Helwan at the entrance to the College de la Sainte Famille. 16.1 x 23.8 cm, 1941-1942; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref195)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Entrance; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Streets/Roads; Students
- Villa balconies on Latif Street in Helwan. 24 x 18 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref196)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Balcony/Terrace; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints
- Group portrait os students with a teacher at the top of a rock during a field trip to the desert. 23.9 x 18 cm, 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref197)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Deserts; Field-trip; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education; Shorts; Students; Teachers
- Statues of Buddha by the water in the Japanese Gardens in Helwan. 18 x 24.2 cm, 1983; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref198)
  Arabic Writing; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Parks; Photographic Prints; Pond; Sculpture; Statues; Trees; Water
- Class portrait. 17.4 x 23.8 cm, 1959-1960; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref199)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Group outdoor portrait of five teachers. 30.4 x 20.9 cm, 1936; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref200)
  Arabic Writing; Beards; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Fezes/Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education; Teachers
- Street view of Helwan. 8.9 x 12.9 cm, May 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref201)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads
- Front view of Orthodox Cemetery. 8.9 x 12.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref202)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Cemeteries; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Orthodox Christianity; Photographic Prints
- Japanese Garden in Helwan. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref203)
  Arabic Writing; Gardens; Gazebo; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Pond; Water
- A priest and a boy standing in water in Suez. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref204)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Suez, Egypt; Water
- Group of students sitting on top of a bridge during field trip. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref205)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Boys; Bridges; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Railways
- Four teachers at a table with a microphone. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1965-1966; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref206)